Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1935-1936, Series 20
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Ro (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Sa (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Sc (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Se (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Slavic (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Sm (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Sororities (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - St (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Mother's Club (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Su (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - T (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Trustees (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Trustees (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Trustees' Fund for Self-Supporting Students (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Tuition (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - U - V (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - United States (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Wa (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Western School Commercial Secretaries (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Wh (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Wo (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Women's Council (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - YMCA (Box 177, Folder 14)
- 1936-1937, Series 21
  - First Honor code Panel (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - A (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - American (Box 177, Folder 18)
  - Anatomy (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Office (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Assistants (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Assistants (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Assistants (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Associated Students (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Ba (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Bacteriology (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Be (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Bequests to the Univ. (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Bi (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Biology, School of (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Bu (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - By (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Ca (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - California Emergency Relief (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - California Emergency Relief (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Endowment (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - Ch (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Chaparral (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Classical Literature (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Co (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Commencement (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Da (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Dean of Men (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Dean of Women (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - College of Dentistry (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Do (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Dormitories (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Economics (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Education (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Education (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Education (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Encina Hall (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Endowment (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Engineering, Education (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 181, Folder 14)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 181, Folder 15)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 181, Folder 16)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - English (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Fa (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Fellowships, Foreign (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Fine Arts (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Fo (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Lawrence Frost Amphitheater Name Contest (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Ga (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - General Education Board (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - Geology (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - German (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Gi (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Gy (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Graphic Arts; Greek (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Haq (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Har (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - He (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - History (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Ho (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Mrs. Timothy Hopkins (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - Housing and Eating Problem (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (Men) (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (Men) (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (Women) (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - I (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Institute of World Affairs (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - J (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Journalism (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Ka (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Ki (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - La (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - Law (Box 184, Folder 14)
  - Legislation (Box 184, Folder 15)
  - Letters, School of (Box 184, Folder 16)
  - Li (Box 184, Folder 17)
  - Library (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Library (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Library (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Ma (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Mathematics (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Mc (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Me (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Medical School - January (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Medical School - February (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Medical School - March (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Medical School - April (Box 185, Folder 11)
  - Medical School - May (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - Medical School - June (Box 185, Folder 13)
  - Medical School - July (Box 185, Folder 14)
  - Medical School - August (Box 185, Folder 15)
  - Medical School - September (Box 185, Folder 16)
  - Medical School - October (Box 185, Folder 17)
  - Medical School - November (Box 185, Folder 18)
  - Medical School - December (Box 185, Folder 19)
  - Medical School - Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Medical School California State (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Church (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Hall (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Men's Council (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Mi (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Miogenic Laboratory (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Mo (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Museum (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Music (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - N (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - National (Box 186, Folder 12)
  - Nursing (Box 186, Folder 13)
  - P (Box 186, Folder 14)
  - Pa (Box 186, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 186, Folder 16)
  - Pathology (Box 186, Folder 17)
  - Pensions (Box 186, Folder 18)
  - Philosophy (Box 186, Folder 19)
  - Physics (Box 186, Folder 20)
  - Physiology (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Pi (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Political Science (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Psychology (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Publicity (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Quad (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Ra (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Radio (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations - Letters (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Registrar (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - Travel Fund denied (Box 187, Folder 15)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Ro (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Sa (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Sc (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Se (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Slavic (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Sm (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Council; Social Service Board (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Sororities (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - St (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Associated (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Band (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Flying Club (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Mothers' Club (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Su (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - T (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Trustees (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Trustees (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Manual, Requests for (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Tuition (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - U-V (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - United States (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Wa (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Western School for Commercial Secretaries (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Wh (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Wo (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Women's Council (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - X,Y,Z (Box 190, Folder 13)
- 1937-1938, Series 22
  - A (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - Appointment Service (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - American (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - Anatomy (Box 190, Folder 18)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Assistants (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Assistants (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Assistants (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Associated Students (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Ba (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Bacteriology (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Be (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Bequests (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Bi (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - President's Courtesy List - Stanford, CA (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Biology, School of (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Biology, School of (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Br (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Bu (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Butano Forest (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Ca (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - California Board of Education (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - California Emergency Relief (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - California Society to Promote Medical Research (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - California Society to Promote Medical Research (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - California Society to Promote Medical Research (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - California Society to Promote Medical Research (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Ch (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Chaparral (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Classics (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Co (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Commencement (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller - Sept. to Feb. (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller - Sept. to Feb. (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller - March to Aug. (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller - March to Aug. (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller - March to Aug. (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Da (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Men (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Women (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Do (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Dormitories (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - E (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Economics (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Education (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Education (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - Education (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Education (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Endowments (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, Mining (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - English (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - Fa (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - Fellowships, Foreign (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Fo (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Ga (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - General Education Board (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Geology (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - German (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Gi (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Gr (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Graphic Art (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Ha (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - He (Box 197, Folder 13)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 197, Folder 14)
  - History (Box 197, Folder 15)
  - Ho (Box 197, Folder 16)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins, Mrs. Timothy (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Housing (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Men (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education - Women (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - I (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Invitations - R.L.W. (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Invitations - R.L.W. (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Invitations - R.L.W. (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Invitations - R.L.W. (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - J (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Journalism (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Junior College (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Ka (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Kl (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - L (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 199, Folder 12)
  - Law (Box 199, Folder 13)
  - Letters, School of (Box 199, Folder 14)
  - Li (Box 199, Folder 15)
  - Library (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Library (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Ma (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - M(a)c (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Mathematics (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Me (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Medical School (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Medical School (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Medical School (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Medical School (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Industrial Hygiene (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Church (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Hall (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Men's Council (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Mi (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Mo (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Museum (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Music (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - N (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - National (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Nursing (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - O (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Pa (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Patents, 1933-34 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Patents, 1935-36 (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Patents, 1936-37 (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Patents, 1937-38 (Box 201, Folder 17)
  - Patents, University Staff (Box 201, Folder 18)
  - Philosophy (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Physics (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Physiology (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Piq (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Political Science (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - President's Office (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Psychology (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Publicity (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Quad (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Ra (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - Radio (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Radio Programs, (1937-40) (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - Programs, Radio - current (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Programs, Radio - current (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Registrar (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Travel Fund - Denied or withdrawn (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Travel Fund - Pending (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Comm. (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Ro (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (Box 204)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Sa (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Sc (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Se (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Slavic (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Sm (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Marriage (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - St (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 204, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Mothers Club (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Su (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - T (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Trustees (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Tuition (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - U-V (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - United States (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - Wa (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Western School for Commercial Secretaries (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Wh (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Wo (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Women's Council (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Women's Council (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - YMCA (Box 206, Folder 9)
- 1938-1939, Series 23
  - A (Box 214, Folder 14)
  - A (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Academic and Alumni Secretary (1) (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Academic and Alumni Secretary (2) (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 214, Folder 15)
  - American (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - American (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - American, March August (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - American (1) (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - American (2) (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - American Medical Association (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (September October) (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (November December) (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (January February) (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (March April) (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (May June) (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - American Social Hygiene Association, (July August) (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - Applications - Positions (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - Applications Positions (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Applications Positions (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Assistants (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Assistants, 1933-34 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Assistants, 1933-34 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Associated Students (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Ba (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Bacteriology (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Be (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Bequests (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Bi (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Biology, School of (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 216, Folder 12)
  - Br (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Bridges, Harry (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Bu (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Budgets (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Butano [Forest lands, part of T. Hopkins estate] (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Butano [Forest lands, part of T. Hopkins estate] (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Butano Forest (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Ca (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - California Board of Education (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - California Emergency Relief (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - California Physician's Service (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - California Physician's Service (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - California society for Promotion of Medical Research (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - California society for Promotion of Medical Research (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - California, University of (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - California, University of (Box 217, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 217, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 217, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 217, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 217, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 217, Folder 13)
  - Ch (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Chaparral (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Classical Literature (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Co (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - College of Dentistry (Box 219, Folder 11)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Commencement (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Communism: testimory by unnamed person on the leading adherents of the Marxian school of political philosophy [case involved a Mr. Bridges] (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller, December, January, February (Box 218, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller, December, January, February (Box 218, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller, March, April, May (Box 218, Folder 12)
  - Comptroller, March, April, May (Box 218, Folder 13)
  - Comptroller, June, July, August (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller, June, July, August (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Conventions (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Conventions (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Da (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Men (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Dean of Men: Amphitheater Incident (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Women (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Do (Box 219, Folder 12)
  - Dog Bill (Amendment No. 2) (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Dog Bill (Amendment No. 2) (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Dormitories (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Economics (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Education (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Education, (March, April, May) (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - Education, (December, January, February) (Box 206, Folder 18)
  - Education (1), (June, July, August) (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Education (2), (June, July, August) (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Education Building (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Endowments (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Engagements (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Engineering Education (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - English (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Fa (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Fellowships Foreign (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Fo (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Football (Box 216, Folder 13)
  - Fraternities (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Friends of Music (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Ga (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - General Education Board (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Geology (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - German (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Gi (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - Gr (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School, Business Administration (Box 208, Folder 13)
  - Graduate School, Business Administration (Box 208, Folder 14)
  - Graduate School, Business Administration (Box 208, Folder 15)
  - Graphic Art (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Ha (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Har (Box 209, Folder 4)